<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Trading Education</string>
    <string name="back">Back</string>
    <string name="balance_refresh_info">Sorry you can refresh your balance only if it lower than 1000$</string>
    <string name="contact_error">Please fill all required fields</string>
    <string name="contact_us">Contact Us</string>
    <string name="down">DOWN</string>
    <string name="down_with">DOWN %d%%</string>
    <string name="exit_app">Exit App</string>
    <string name="faq">FAQ</string>
    <string name="faq_five">Are the data in the chart real?</string>
    <string name="faq_five_desc">The data in the chart are real and correspond to market quotes.</string>
    <string name="faq_four">How to choose a broker?</string>
    <string name="faq_four_desc">When choosing a broker, pay attention to the following criteria: licensing and regulation, reputation and user reviews, trading conditions (minimum deposit, bet sizes, profitability), availability of a demo account, quality of customer support, and availability of educational materials.</string>
    <string name="faq_one">How to trade on the simulator?</string>
    <string name="faq_one_desc">To trade on the simulator, choose a trading pair, then select the trade direction UP or DOWN. You can stop the bet at any moment to calculate the profit.</string>
    <string name="faq_seven">What is the best time to trade?</string>
    <string name="faq_seven_desc">The best time to trade depends on the selected asset. For example, currency pairs are most active during the overlapping trading sessions of major financial centers (London, New York, Tokyo). For stocks, the optimal time is during the trading hours of the exchanges on which they are listed.</string>
    <string name="faq_six">The prices in the chart are not updating, what should I do?</string>
    <string name="faq_six_desc">From time to time, market activity slows down, usually during weekends and holidays. Check your internet connection.</string>
    <string name="faq_test">Donec tempus pharetra leo sit amet semper. Orci varius natoque penatibus et magnis dis parturient montes, nascetur ridiculus mus.\n\nNunc a turpis lectus. Nullam urna odio, lobortis quis ipsum ac, varius vulputate ipsum. Mauris et orci dictum, convallis velit nec, lacinia justo.\n\nDuis facilisis arcu a dapibus tincidunt. Aenean orci augue, tempor nec diam vel, auctor ultrices libero.</string>
    <string name="faq_three">Can I earn money on currency rate differences?</string>
    <string name="faq_three_desc">Yes, trading binary options through a broker allows you to earn money on currency rate differences. To do this, select a currency pair, predict the rate movement, and open \"higher/lower\" options or other types of options based on your forecast. However, this application is only an educational simulator, and you cannot earn money using it.</string>
    <string name="faq_two">How to withdraw money?</string>
    <string name="faq_two_desc">This application is a trading simulator. Since you are not using your own funds for trading operations, you cannot either lose or earn money using this application.</string>
    <string name="first_name">First name</string>
    <string name="how_to_play_description_four">Risk management is crucial in Forex trading. Never risk more than you can afford to lose. Use stop-loss orders to limit potential losses, and always consider the risk-reward ratio of your trades. Diversify your portfolio to spread risk.</string>
    <string name="how_to_play_description_one">Before diving into Forex trading, it\'s crucial to understand the basics. Learn about currency pairs, how the market works, and the factors that influence currency values. Familiarize yourself with key concepts such as pips, leverage, and margin.</string>
    <string name="how_to_play_description_three">A solid trading strategy is vital for consistency and success in the Forex market. Decide whether you prefer technical analysis, fundamental analysis, or a combination of both. Set clear entry and exit points, and always stick to your strategy.</string>
    <string name="how_to_play_description_two">Selecting the right broker is essential for successful Forex trading. Look for a broker with a good reputation, competitive spreads, robust trading platforms, and excellent customer support. Ensure they are regulated by a reputable financial authority.</string>
    <string name="how_to_play_market">How to Play\non Forex Market</string>
    <string name="how_to_play_title_four">Manage Your Risk</string>
    <string name="how_to_play_title_one">Learn the Basics</string>
    <string name="how_to_play_title_three">Develop a Trading Strategy</string>
    <string name="how_to_play_title_two">Choose a Reliable Broker</string>
    <string name="info">The price forecast widget indicates the likely direction of future prices.\n\nFor instance, a \"down\" value of 70% means that 70% of the forecasted trades are expected to be \"down\", helping you adjust your trading direction.</string>
    <string name="investment">Investment Tools</string>
    <string name="investment_desc">How to invest to make a profit</string>
    <string name="investment_description_four">ETFs are similar to mutual funds but trade on stock exchanges like individual stocks. They offer diversification by holding a basket of different assets, such as stocks, bonds, or commodities. ETFs are cost-effective, transparent, and flexible, making them a popular investment tool for both beginners and experienced investors.</string>
    <string name="investment_description_one">Stocks represent ownership in a company and offer potential for high returns. By buying shares, you become a partial owner of the company and can profit through capital appreciation and dividends. It\'s essential to research companies, understand their business models, and analyze financial statements before investing.</string>
    <string name="investment_description_three">Mutual funds pool money from many investors to purchase a diversified portfolio of stocks, bonds, or other securities. They are managed by professional portfolio managers and offer a convenient way to invest without the need to pick individual stocks or bonds. Mutual funds can cater to various investment goals, risk tolerances, and time horizons.</string>
    <string name="investment_description_two">Bonds are debt securities issued by governments, municipalities, or corporations. When you purchase a bond, you\'re lending money to the issuer in exchange for regular interest payments and the return of the bond\'s face value at maturity. Bonds are generally less risky than stocks and provide steady income, making them a good tool for diversification.</string>
    <string name="investment_title_four">Exchange-Traded Funds (ETFs)</string>
    <string name="investment_title_one">Stocks</string>
    <string name="investment_title_three">Mutual Funds</string>
    <string name="investment_title_two">Bonds</string>
    <string name="language">Language: %s</string>
    <string name="last_name">Last name</string>
    <string name="message">Message</string>
    <string name="message_sent">Message sent</string>
    <string name="next">Next</string>
    <string name="novice">Novice</string>
    <string name="profit">Profit</string>
    <string name="send">Send</string>
    <string name="stop">STOP</string>
    <string name="total_profit">Total profit</string>
    <string name="trade_close_price">Trade close price</string>
    <string name="trade_close_time">Trade close time</string>
    <string name="trade_fail">Why do traders Fail?</string>
    <string name="trade_fail_desc">4 common traders mistakes</string>
    <string name="trade_fail_description_four">Successful trading requires an understanding of market conditions and adapting strategies accordingly. Ignoring market trends, news events, and economic indicators can result in poorly timed trades. Staying informed and flexible is key to navigating different market environments.</string>
    <string name="trade_fail_description_one">Many traders jump into the market without a solid trading plan. A well-defined plan includes entry and exit strategies, risk management rules, and specific goals. Without a plan, traders often make impulsive decisions based on emotions rather than logic.</string>
    <string name="trade_fail_description_three">Overtrading occurs when traders take too many trades, often due to a desire to recoup losses quickly or capitalize on perceived opportunities. This can lead to exhaustion, poor decision-making, and substantial financial losses. Sticking to a well-planned trading strategy can help avoid overtrading.</string>
    <string name="trade_fail_description_two">Failing to manage risk properly is a common reason for trading failure. Traders might risk too much on a single trade, leading to significant losses. Using tools like stop-loss orders and limiting the amount of capital at risk on each trade can mitigate this risk.</string>
    <string name="trade_fail_title_four">Ignoring Market Conditions</string>
    <string name="trade_fail_title_one">Lack of a Trading Plan</string>
    <string name="trade_fail_title_three">Overtrading</string>
    <string name="trade_fail_title_two">Poor Risk Management</string>
    <string name="trade_history">Trade history</string>
    <string name="trade_open_price">Trade open price</string>
    <string name="trade_open_time">Trade open time</string>
    <string name="trade_time">Trade time</string>
    <string name="up">UP</string>
    <string name="up_with">UP %d%%</string>
    <string name="why_invest">Why Invest?</string>
    <string name="why_invest_desc">4 reasons to invest money</string>
    <string name="why_invest_description_four">Investing provides a source of passive income through dividends, interest, or rental income. This supplemental income can offer financial security and even enable early retirement, supporting your lifestyle and goals.</string>
    <string name="why_invest_description_one">Investing helps grow your wealth over time. By putting your money into assets like stocks, bonds, or real estate, you can earn returns that outpace inflation, increasing your purchasing power and making your money work for you.</string>
    <string name="why_invest_description_three">Investing protects your money from inflation, which erodes purchasing power over time. By earning returns that exceed inflation, you maintain or increase your wealth, ensuring your standard of living is preserved.</string>
    <string name="why_invest_description_two">Investing helps you achieve financial goals efficiently, whether it\'s buying a home, funding education, or planning for retirement. A well-planned investment strategy can turn your dreams into reality by providing the necessary financial resources.</string>
    <string name="why_invest_title_four">Generate Passive Income</string>
    <string name="why_invest_title_one">Grow Your Wealth</string>
    <string name="why_invest_title_three">Beat Inflation</string>
    <string name="why_invest_title_two">Achieve Financial Goals</string>
</resources>